Guide to the Francis B. (Francis Butler) Loomis Papers: microfilm, 1897-1939
Department of Special Collections
- Descendants of Joseph Loomis in America and His Antecedents in the Old World, Series 8; 1 microfilm reel
Orr, Clair A. Roll IV Book 3
Osbon, B. S. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Otis, Harrison G. Roll IV Book 3
Oulahan, Richard V. Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 22
Outlook Roll V Folder 23
Ovay, M. S. Roll III Book 1
Oyster, George M. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Ozmun, Edward H. Roll IV Book 5 Roll V Folder 22
Padberg, E. Roll IV Book 4
Page, Walter H. Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Paish, George Roll V Folder 24
Palmer, F. W. Roll III Book 1
Palmer, Henry Roll III Book 2
Palmer, Percy S. Roll IV Book 4
Panama Canal Roll V Book 19, Book 20, Book 23, Book 24, Folder 25
Panama Railway Company Roll V Folder 19
Paquet, Norbert A. Roll V Folder 19
Paquet and Company Roll V Folder 19
Paris Daily Herald Roll V Folder 24
Parish, W. H. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Parker, Frank Roll V Folder 19
Parker, Gardner T. Roll III Book 1
Parker, George F. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Parker, Julius Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Parsons, James R. Roll IV Book 3
Partridge, Frank C. Roll III Book 1
Patrick, John T. Roll III Book 1
Patterson, A. V. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Patterson Institute Roll IV Book 3
Patterson, William A. Roll IV Book 5
Patton, [?] Roll V Book 23, Folder 24
Paul, B. H. Roll V Folder 22
Paul, J. de J. Roll IV Book 4
Payne, Christopher H. Roll IV Book 4
Peabody, George F. Roll IV Book 4
Peale, G. P. Roll IV Book 4
Pedicaris, Ion Roll V Folder 25
Peixotto, G. D. M. Roll IV Book 4
Peixotto, Percy Roll V Folder 24
Penfield, Forde C. Roll III Book 2
Penfield, William L. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 19
Penrose, Boris Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Pepper, Charles M. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Prez Triane, Eduardo Roll IV Book 4
Prez, G. B. Roll IV Book 3
Perhacs, W. Emil Roll III Book 2
Perkins, George C. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5 Roll V Book 20, Book 21, Folder 22
Perrin, L. Valerein Roll IV Book 3
Perter, Horace Roll III Book 2
Pettit, J. W. Roll IV Book 5
Phelan, James D. Roll V Book 23, Folder 24
Philip, Hoffman Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Phillips, H. C. Roll V Book 21, Folder 22
Phillips, Lee Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Phillips, Roland Roll IV Book 3
Phillips, William C. Roll V Folder 22
Pickands Brown and Company Roll V Folder 22
Pierce, Herbert H. Roll IV Book 4
Pierson, P. E. Roll IV Book 3
Pike, William J. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 5
Pillsbury, John E. Roll IV Book 3
Pinchot, Gifford Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 23
Pittman, Key Roll V Folder 25
Planches, Baron des Roll IV Book 4
Platt, Orville H. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Platt, Thomas C. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Plumacher, Eugene H. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Book 21, Folder 23
Pool, A. S. Roll IV Book 4
Porter, Horace Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Porter, Linn B. Roll IV Book 3
Porter, Steve Roll V Folder 24
Porters de la Fosse, des Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Post Express Roll III Book 1
Potbury, Edwin Roll IV Book 4
Potomac Electric Power Company Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Potter, Julian Roll III Book 2
Powell, William T. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Prather, Thomas Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Pratt, J. J. Roll IV Book 3
Prestry, Frank Roll IV Book 4
Pressing and Orr Roll III Book 2
The Press Magazine Roll IV Book 4
Price, Clarence Roll IV Book 4
Proctor, Redfield Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Proskauer, Samuel Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Puhl, M. O. Roll III Book 1
Pulido, Augusto F. Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Pulitzer, Joseph Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 20
Purington, William A. Roll III Book 1
Purinton, T. B. Roll III Book 2
Pyle, H. Roll III Book 2
Queen City Club Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Rabbits, William Roll III Book 2
Raikes, Arthur S. Roll III Book 2
Rainey, Henry T. Roll IV Book 4
Ralston, Jackson H. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Ranolds, T. L. Roll III Book 2
Ray, Nathaniel Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Redfield, Redfield and Lydon Roll III Book 2
Redman, Walter C. Roll III Book 1
Reed, Charles A. L. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Reed, Charles W. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Book 21, Book 22, Folder 23
Reform in the Consular Service See Loomis, F. B. Roll V Folder 23
Reid, James Whitelaw Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Reynolds, James B. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Riano, Juan Roll III Book 2
Ribble, George W. Roll III Book 1
Rice, Harry E. Roll III Book 2
Richards, William A. Roll III Book 1
Richardson, Charles Roll IV Book 3
Richardson, William Roll V Folder 24
Richmond Inner Harbor Project Roll V Folder 24
Riddle, John N. Roll IV Book 3
Rives, George B. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Robbins, Harry W. Roll IV Book 4
Robbins, Raymond Roll V Folder 23
Robinson, Albert G. Roll IV Book 4
Robinson, C. L. F. Roll IV Book 4
Robertson, W. Henry Roll IV Book 4
Roca, Julia A. Roll IV Book 5
Rockhill, W. W. Roll IV Book 3
Rodenberg, [?] Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Rogers, J. Linn Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Rogers, Richard H. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Rojas, P. Ezequiel Roll IV Book 4
Roosa, I. P. Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Roosevelt, Edith Roll IV Book 4
Roosevelt, Franklin Roll V Folder 25
Roosevelt, George W. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Roosevelt, Theodore Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Book 19, Book 20, Book 23, Book 24, Folder 25
Root, Elihu Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5 Roll V Book 21, Book 22, Book 23, Book 24, Folder 25
Rose, I. R. Roll IV Book 3
Ross, John A. Roll IV Book 3
Rowe, L. S. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Rowell, Chester Roll V Book 23, Folder 24
Royal Dutch Oil Company Roll V Folder 24
Russell, Lucy D. Roll IV Book 4
Russell, William W. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 5 Roll V Book 19, Folder 22
Ryan, Thomas Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Sachs, George P. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Sacramento Union Roll V Folder 23
Saint Louis Centennial Celebration Roll V Folder 23
Saint Louis Times Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Sakai, Tadusaki Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Saks, Joseph I. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Sampson, Archibald J. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Sanchez, James F. Roll III Book 2
Sands, W. F. Roll IV Book 4
Sargent, Nathan Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Ibn Saul, King of Arabia Roll V Folder 25
Saum, [?] Roll V Folder 22
Sawter, George Roll IV Book 4
Scaffer, J. C. Roll III Book 2
Scandella, F. Roll IV Book 3
Schaeffer, J. C. Roll IV Book 4
Schieren, Charles A. Roll III Book 2
Schmidlapp, J. G. Roll III Book 2
Schmidtlapp, J. J. Roll V Folder 19
Schonburg, Arthur A. Roll III Book 2
Schwalbe, Otto Roll IV Book 3
Scott, H. T. Roll III Book 1
Scott, John Winfield Roll IV Book 3
Scott, N. B. Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 23
Scruggs, William L. Roll III Book 1
Scrymser, James A. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Seaman, Louis L. Roll IV Book 4
Seeger, Eugene Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Seidmore, G. H. Roll IV Book 4
Servat, Ferdinand Roll III Book 2
Shaffer, J. C. Roll IV Book 3
Shallenberger, W. S. Roll III Book 2
Sharp, Hunter Roll IV Book 3
Sharpe, Amor W. Roll IV Book 4
Shaw, Albert Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Shaw, Howland Roll V Folder 25
Shaw, Leslie M. Roll IV Book 3
Shell Oil Company Roll V Book 24, Folder 25
Sherrill, Charlie Roll V Folder 25
Shugio, Heremich Roll V Folder 21
Schuwalter, E. M. Roll IV Book 3
Simms, F. McL. Roll III Book 2
Skiff, Frederick J. V. Roll V Folder 21
Skinner, Robert P. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4 Roll V Book 19, Book 24, Folder 25
Slater, Robert Y. Roll IV Book 3
Sleicher, John A. Roll IV Book 4
Smedley, Matilda M. Roll IV Book 4
Smiley, Albert K. Roll V Folder 22
Smith, Alvin Roll IV Book 3
Smith, Charles E. Roll IV Book 4
Smith, Charles Sprague Roll III Book 2
Smith, Mrs. Elizabeth Roll III Book 2
Smith, Mrs. Florence H. Roll III Book 1
Smith, Harry C. Roll III Book 2
Smith, James E. Roll V Folder 23
Smith, R. A. C. Roll IV Book 4
Smith, Roderick Roll IV Book 3
Smith, S. Edwin Roll IV Book 4
Snodgrass, John F. Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 22
Snyder, Harry F. Roll III Book 1, Book 2
The Social Register Association Roll IV Book 4
Social Register Company Roll IV Book 3
Sorsby, William B. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Southard, George F. Roll IV Book 4
Spanish Legation Roll IV Book 3
Speaker, C. F. Roll III Book 1
Speck von Sternberg, [?] Roll III Book 1
Speiers, Frederick Roll IV Book 4
Sperry, C. S. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Speyer, James Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Spier, Edgar Roll V Folder 23
Spooner, George C. Roll III Book 2
Spooner, John C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Sprague, Richard L. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Springfield National Bank Roll III Book 1
Sproule, Robert G. Roll V Folder 24
Squires, Herbert G. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Stalo, Edmund P. Roll IV Book 3
Standard Oil Company Roll V Book 24, Folder 25
Stanton, Theodore Roll IV Book 4
Stearns, F. W. Roll V Folder 24
Steinhart, Frank Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Sternburg, George M. Roll III Book 1
Stevens, Frederick C. Roll III Book 1
Stevens, G. W. Roll III Book 2
Stevens, William B. Roll III Book 1
Stewart, Alexander M. Roll V Folder 21
Stewart, Chase Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Stewart, P. M. Roll IV Book 3
Stoggson, W. J. Roll III Book 2
Stone, Melville W. Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 22
Storer, Bellamy Roll III Book 2
Strauss, Oscar S. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Strayer, L. W. Roll IV Book 4
Strobridge, Nelson Roll V Folder 21
Strubbery, F. C. Roll III Book 2
Surez, Francesco de P. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Suesman, A. L. Roll III Book 1
Sullivan, Edward J. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Swalm, Albert W. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Swalm, Mrs. A. W. Roll III Book 1
Swan, A. R. Roll III Book 2
Sylvester, Richard Roll IV Book 4
Symonds, F. W. Roll IV Book 3
Symons, Thomas W. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Symons, W. L. Roll IV Book 4
Taft, Charles P. Roll V Folder 20
Taft, H. F. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Taft, William H. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4 Roll V Book 19, Book 20, Book 22, Folder 23
Tailor, G. Cornell Roll IV Book 4
Takahira, Kogoro Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Book 21, Folder 22
Tarrisse, Edwin Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Taylor, H. C. Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Taylor, Mrs. H. C. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Taylor, Julian Roll III Book 2
Taylor, Robert W. Roll IV Book 4
Taylor, Samuel Roll IV Book 4
Taylor, W. W. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll V Folder 19
Texas Oil Corporation Roll V Folder 25
Thackara, Alexander M. Roll IV Book 4
Thaddeus, H. Jones Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Thieriot, Jacob H. Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Thomas, Miss Grace Roll III Book 2
Thomas, Lot Roll III Book 2
Thompson, D. E. Roll IV Book 3
Thompson, Howard Roll IV Book 4
Thompson, Joseph O. Roll III Book 1
Thompson, Robert M. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Thorndike, Harry Hill Roll III Book 1
Thwing, Charles S. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Tillman, Benjamin R. Roll IV Book 3
Tingler, Edmund W. Roll IV Book 3
Tobin, Dick Roll V Folder 24
Tokalon Wine Company Roll IV Book 3
Tokyo Exposition Roll V Book 21, Folder 23
Tomey, R. E. S. Roll IV Book 4
Torsesy, Sargaseta M. Roll III Book 2
Tower, Charlemagne Roll IV Book 3
Townsend, Charles E. Roll IV Book 4
Townsend, George Alfred Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Townsend, Lawrence Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Traverst, [?] Roll V Folder 22
Trueblood, Bejamin F. Roll IV Book 3
Tubbins, F. Roll III Book 1
Tuells, John Roll III Book 2
Tyler, George C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 22
Uchida, Sadazuchi Roll IV Book 3
Union Savings Bank and Trust Company Roll III Book 1
Van Buren, Harold S. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
van Dyne, Frederic Roll IV Book 3
van Giskra, Karl Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
van Middeldyk, R. A. Roll III Book 2
Van Norman, Louis E. Roll III Book 2
van Roijan, J. H. Roll III Book 2
van Tuyll von Serookerken, L.
Varadhara, Phya A. Roll IV Book 3
Venezuelan Legation Roll III Book 1
Vignaud, Henry Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Villa, Poncho [Doroteo Arango] Roll V Folder 23
Villard, H. S. Roll V Folder 25
Vincentini, C. Roll IV Book 3
Volkmor, William H. Roll III Book 1
Wada, Hikojiro Roll V Folder 23
Wadsworth, B. Roll V Folder 24
W. B. Hibbs and Company Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Wagner, Belle Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Walbridge, C. P. Roll IV Book 3
Walker, Ernest G. Roll IV Book 4
Walker, John G. Roll III Book 2 Roll V Folder 21
Wallace, Thomas R. Roll IV Book 4
Wallis, Edgar A. Roll V Folder 19
Walsh, Thomas Roll IV Book 4
Wanamaker, John Roll III Book 1
Wands, Ernest H. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Ware, Eugene F. Roll III Book 1
Warner, B. H. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Warren, Francis E. Roll IV Book 4
Washburn, W. D. Roll IV Book 3
Washington Gaslight Company Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Washington, Horace L. Roll III Book 2
Waterloo, Stanley Roll IV Book 4
Watson, David K. Roll IV Book 4
Watts, Ethelbert Roll III Book 1
Wauters, David S. Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Webster, Daniel Roll V Folder 22
Wedemeyer, W. W. Roll IV Book 4
Weeks, John Roll V Folder 24
Weile, Francois Roll IV Book 4
Welles, Sumner Roll V Folder 25
Wellman, Walter Roll IV Book 4
Welsch, C. A. Roll III Book 2
Westcott, Burton Roll III Book 1
Westcott, Horace Roll IV Book 3
Westcott and Story Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Wetmore, R. C. Roll III Book 2
Wheeler, Post Roll V Folder 21
White, A. B. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
White, Charles W. Roll III Book 2
White, Henry Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Whitney, Casper Roll V Folder 19
Wiborg, Frank B. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Wilbur, Ray Lyman Roll V Folder 24
Wilcox, Paul Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Wilder, R. W. Roll III Book 1
Wildman, Edwin Roll IV Book 4
Willets, Gilson Roll V Folder 22
Williams, Talcott Roll III Book 2
Williams, T. S. Roll III Book 2
Wills, Henry M. Roll III Book 3
Wilson, George T. Roll III Book 2
Wilson, Henry L. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4 Roll V Folder 22
Wilson, Huntington Roll III Book 1
Wilson, James H. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Wilson, Woodrow Roll V Book 23, Folder 24
Winchester Repeating Arms Company Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Winslow, Alfred A. Roll IV Book 4
Winthrop, Beekman Roll IV Book 4
Witte, Seigey Y. Roll V Folder 20
Wolf, Simon Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Wood, H. P. Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Book 21, Folder 22
Wood, Mrs. Leonard Roll V Folder 23
Woodard, J. H. Roll III Book 2
Woodford, Stewart L. Roll III Book 1
Woodford, Stewart M. Roll IV Book 3
Woodruf, Walter W. Roll IV Book 4
Woodward and Lothrop Roll III Book 1
Woodward, William C. Roll III Book 1
The World Roll IV Book 5
The Worlds Work Roll V Folder 23
Worman, James H. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Worman, Thomas H. Roll IV Book 4
Wright, Luke C. Roll IV Book 3
Xander, Charles Roll IV Book 4
Ybarra, Thomas Roll III Book 2
Yela, Don Joaquin Roll III Book 2
Yerkes, John M. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Young, George W. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Yun, Chung Kim Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Zen, William J. Roll III Book 1
Zumeta, Caesar Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Selected Correspondents
Adee, Alvey
Alcal, F.
Andrade, Ignacio
Ashikama, Francis
Bacon, Robert
Bancroft, Frederick
Barrett, John
Bas-Ironside, [?]
Bean, Henry W.
Beasley, Delilah I.
Beaupre, A. M.
Bonte, George W.
Bryce, James
Bunau-Varilla, Philippe
Burleson, A. S.
Burton, Theodore F.
Butler, Nicholas Murray
Campillo, Agustine
Cararris, J.A.O.
Carnegie, Andrew
Carnegie, Louise W.
Carpenter, Fred W.
Carr, Wilbur
Carter, George W.
Cassini, Count
Chadwick, F. E.
Chapin, F. L.
Cherry, Albert
Clarkson, J. S.
Coe, F. W.
Colbert, Jessica
Colijn, H.
Conde, Fabricio
Conkling, Howard
Coolidge, Calvin
Corbin, Edythe Patterson
Cowles, Anna Roosevelt
Cox, James M.
Crichfield, George W.
Crocker, William H.
Cuneo, Pietro
Davidson, James W.
Davison, Henry P.
Dawes, Charles G.
Dawson, T. C.
Day, William R.
Dean, Charles R.
Delfino, Antonio E.
DeLima, E.
Denby, Edwin
DeVault, Charles L.
Dewart, William T.
Dewey, George
Diaz, Porfirio
Dillingham, A. C.
Dolge, Rudolf
DuBois, James T.
Elkins, Stephen B.
Feuille, Frank
Firter, John W.
Foch, Ferdinand
Foord, John
Foraker, Joseph B.
Freiberg, Morris
Frelinghuyser, Fred
Frick, H. C.
Frieberg, Maurice J.
Fullotton, W. Norton
Gardener, Frank S.
Gary, Elbert H.
Geiger, Alfred L.
Gibson, Harvey
Gibson, Hugh
Gillett, J.
Goldschmidt, Louis
Grant-Duff, A. C.
Greene, Francis V.
Grew, Joseph
Grey, Harvey H.
Griscom, Lloyd C.
Grosscup, Peter S.
Haggard, W.
Hammond, John Hays
Handy, F. W.
Hanna, Edward, Archbishop
Hanna, Marcus
Hanna, Philip
Harding, Warren G.
Harrison, Benjamin
Haskell, Henry S.
Hay, Clara S.
Hay, John
Hays, William
Heistand, H. O. S.
Henry, Charles L.
Herrick, Myron T.
Hill, David J.
Hill, William C.
Hirst, F. W.
Holman, Alfred
Holt, Hamilton
Hoover, Herbert
Houghton, A. B.
Hughes, Charles E.
Hull, Cordell
Hurst, Carl Bailey
Ishii, Kikujiko
Jaurett, A. F.
Johnson, Henry U.
Johnson, Hiram
Joubert, Emilio C.
Jusserand, Jean Jules
Karrasch, F.
Kellogg, Frank B.
Kenyon, William S.
Kerens, Richard C.
Knowles, Horace
Knox, Frank
Knox, Pilander C.
Kowasky, Henry T.
Labby, William H.
Laidlow, Robert
Lanfield, Jerone
Langenberg, H. F.
Langerman, James
Lansing, Robert
Lay, Julius
Lcon, A. C.
Little, W. S.
Locb, William, Jr.
Lockwood, Edwin C.
Lodge, Henry C.
Longworth, Nicholas
Loomis, Charles W.
Loomis, Elizabeth Mast
Maddox, Samuel
Mason, Frank
Matsudaira, Tsunco
Mayers, Charles
McAdoo, William G.
McCormick, Robert S.
McCoy, Frank
McKenney, F. D.
Mellon, A. W.
Mercado, Lorenzo
Merritt, R. F. R.
Michelson, Albert
Micholson, D.
Millet, Frank D.
Mills, Ogden L.
Miyoaka, Tsunejiro
Montauban, E.
Moody, W. H.
Moore, John B.
Morgan, Charles P.
Morgan, Douglas A.
Morse, S. F. B.
Morton, Paul
Nabucof, Joaquin
Naumburg, A.
Newcomb, William A.
Newshall, W. Mays
O'Connor, Basil
Odell, H. Allen
O'Laughlin, John C.
Olavarria, J. A.
Olcott, R. Morgan
Overstreet, Jesse
Paquet, Norbert, A.
Paredes, Antonio
Parker, Frank
Parmelee, James
Patchin, Robert H.
Penfield, William L.
Pepper, Charles M.
Perkins, George C.
Phelan, James D.
Pickleman, Sebastian
Pierce, Herbert H. D.
Pillsbury, E. S.
Porter, Horace
Prostkauer, Saul
Purbrey, Eugene
Reid, J. Whitelaw
Reynolds, J. B.
Rockefeller, John D., Jr.
Rogers, Edith N.
Roosevelt, Theodore
Rowell, Chester
Royce, L. W.
Sakai, Tadusaki
Sampson, William T.
Sargent, Nathan
Sharp, Amor W.
Shaw, Albert
Shortridge, Samuel M.
Sigsbee, Charles D.
Skiff, Frederick J.
Skinner, Robert P.
Smith, Charles E.
Speck von Sternberg, Baron
Speransky, Julia G.
Speyer, James
Steinhart, [?]
Stimson, Henry L.
Stoddard, Henry L.
Stokes, W. E. D.
Straus, Oscar S.
Taft, Robert A.
Taft, William H.
Thayer, W. Roscoe
Thompson, John
Tower, Charlemagne
Townsend George A.
Underwood, Rufus A.
van Loon, Hendrick Willem
Vavasour-Noel, John
Vignauer, Henry
Wada, Hikojiro
Wadsworth, James W., Jr
Warren, Charles B.
Weeks, John W.
Welles, Sumner
White, Albert B.
White, Henry
Wickersham, George W.
Wilbur, Ray Lyman
Wilson, Henry P.
Wood, Leonard
Woodford, Stewart
Wright, Robert K.
Wurlitzer, Howard
Yeiser, H. C.
Young, Ella
Zumeta, Caesar
Publications Included in the Loomis Papers
U.S. Government Publications by Title
Before the International Tribunal of The Hague, Great Britain, Germany, and Italy Against Venezuela. [Washington, D.C.]: n.d.
Business Opportunities in Portuguese Colonies Advance Sheets of Consular Reports No. 1448. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, 1902.
In the Matter of Mr. Herbert M. Bowen, United States Minister to Venezuela, Against Mr. Francis B. Loomis, First Assistant Secretary of State, and the Counter Charges of Mr. Loomis Against Mr. Bowen. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, 1905.
In the Matter of United States and Venezuela Company Against the United States of Venezuela. n.p., [1905].
In the Matter of United States and Venezuela Company Against the United States of Venezuela, Brief for Petitioner. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, [1905].
Memorandum for the Secretary of State on the Dominion Republic. n.p., [1904].
Opening Argument and Reply for the United States by William I., Penfield before the Arbitration Tribunal of The Hague. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, 1903.
Special Message of the President of the United States Concerning the Panama Canal. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, 1906.
Venezuela. Bulletin No. 34, (February, 1892). Bureau of the American Republics. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, n.d.
Venezuelan Protocols. Herbert W. Bowen. Washington, D.C.: Government Printing Office, 1903.
Other Publications
Baker, Henry D., Trinidad and Venezuela-Asphalt Lakes. Trinidad: Franklin's Electric Printery, 1924.
Baravelli, G.C., The Last Stronghold of Slavery. Rome: Societa Editrice di Novissima, 1935.
Bunau-Varilla, Philippe, The Strait of Panama, A Lecture Before the Commercial Club of Cincinnati. January 19, 1924. n.p.,n.d.
Drake, Anthony (Ed.), Venezuela II. No. 7 (June 1899). Caracas: American Publishing Co., n.d.
Fisher, George J. B., Le Sauvetage du Canal de Panama. Paris: Librairie Plon, 1934
Loomis, Elisha, Descendants of Joseph Loomis in America and his Antecedents in the Old World. 1909.
Marion, H., John Paul Jones' Last Cruise and Final Resting Place. Washington, D.C.: 1906.
Perkins, H. J., Notes on British Guiana and Its Gold Industry. Sampson, Low, Marston Company, Ltd., [1907].
Exposicin Histrica (The Secession of Panama). Panama: n.p. 1911.
The Italo Ethiopian Dispute Abstracts from the Memorandum of the Italian Government to the League of Nations. Rome: Societa Editrice di Novissima, 1935.
Santo Domingo. Reprint from the New York Commercial, April 20, 1906.
Santo Domingo Treaty. Reprint from the Evening Post of New York, March II, 1905.
The Santo Domingo Treaty and Its Relation to the Commercial Interests of the United States. Report by the Committee on Foreign and Insular Trade, New York Board of Trade and Transportation. New York, March 28, 1906. n.p., n.d.
Articles by and About Loomis
Loomis, Francis B., The Administration and Santo Domingo. The Independent 56 (1904): 459.
[A Statesman]. The Government's Position on Panama. The Independent 55 (1903): 283-2841.
Our Diplomatic Service and It's [sic] Needs. Public Opinion 40 (1906): 324-329.
The Price of Peace Judicial Settlement of International Disputes. Conference at Washington. (Dec. 15-17, 1910) n.p., n.d.
Proposed Reorganization of the Consular Service. The North American Review 182 (1906): 356-373.
Eminent Leaders of the American Red Cross. The Red Cross Courier. March 1, 1928: 13.
Published Speeches by Francis B. Loomis
Address of Welcome on Behalf of the President, to the Delegates to the Twelfth Conference of the Interparliamentary Union. Delivered at St. Louis, September 12, 1904, Advocate of Peace 66 (1904): 185-187.
Attitude of the United States Towards Other American Powers. Reprinted from The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science. July 1905. n.p., n.d.
The Position of the United States on the American Continent. Annual Address at Philadelphia, April 17, 1903: n.p., n.d.
The Position of the United States on the American Continent, Some Phases of the Monroe Doctrine. Reprinted from The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science. July 1903, Philadelphia: n.p., n.d.
Remarks...At the International Dinner of The New York Southern Society. April 26, 1906. Washington, D.C.: Press of Gibson Brothers, 1906.
Some Phases of the Panama Question Delivered at the Twill Club, New York, December 15, 1903. n.p., n.d.
Items Removed from the Collection
Maybeck, Bernard R., Palace of Fine Arts and Lagoon. San Francisco: Paul Elder and Company, 1915.
Loomis Materials in Other Repositories